The World Conference, known
as the Reverie, has concluded.
It is a meeting that
occurs every four years,
where a council of 50
world leaders gather,
representing some of the 170 nations
affiliated under the world government.
As it often does, the event ended
with a great sense of uncertainty.
The representatives went home
without much reassurance.
Then one week later,
goodness,
that's always such a trek!
It's good to be home.
Heading up to the surface world
always takes so much out of me.
I wanted to thank you for
escorting us back safely, Mr.
Luffy's grandpa.
I bet that excursion must have
been pretty draining on you.
Sounding tuggered out there, Neptune.
You could say that again.
Garp, why don't you take a load off
and get some well-deserved rest?
Well, maybe I'll stay for a cup of
tea or two, but not much longer.
Wouldn't want to be lax
at a time like this.
The reverie always
seems to result in chaos
To put it simply,
when you have 50 heads of state
in the same room You can't
expect them to get along Each
country is only thinking about
their own problems The major
powers will stare each other
down And let the smaller nations
squabble over this and that
If you've got the
resources and technology,
you're the shot caller
huh they say all countries
are equal but those words
never hold any weight
as long as there are wealth
and religious differences
that will never be true
equality unfortunately
when it's time to shake
they grin and stomp each
other's feet under the
table these rulers can
speak for themselves but
can they speak for all
their citizens or the
citizens of other nations?
The round table is nothing
but a myth. Quite true.
As they say, you could cut the
tension in that room with a knife.
The source of that friction is
a history that runs deep indeed,
and we are no exception.
Alas, the issues of the past are
not swept away so easily or quietly.
The way I see it, as long as no
blood spilled at the end of the day,
then I'm willing to call it peace.
This year's reverie was bad though, maybe
I should have said something sooner,
but there was an incident that
happened—I haven't told anyone yet.
It took place right after
the reverie was dismissed.
I got a report when I
was leaving on the ship.
Let me preface this by saying the navy is
using everything it's
got to settle this mess!
Don't fear humans or the
surface either—what could have?
could have
happened.
The report must have been rather
serious for you to act this way, Garp.
It concerns
the Alabasta Kingdom.
Please say it isn't so.
Princess Phoebe.
Shortly after the reverie was dismissed,
the reporters were abuzz at the
headquarters of the World Economic Journal.
How are all these things
happening at Lawrence?
It's one thing after another. Jeez.
We need We need a catchy
headline for this!
Which one is going on the front page?
Hey!
This is big for us!
Nothing rakes in cash like an obituary!
That's the cover story, then!
Patience!
The resolution they passed is juicy, too!
And there was an attempted murder!
So I have a plan! What? Boss!
For the first time ever,
we're running dual covers!
A story on front and back! Okay!
Sir, you've got a telegram
from the government.
There's a check?
Oh, look at those zeros!
So they want me to cover up one
of these hot stories, do they?
Well, let's see which one it is.
I ain't passing on the
biggest scoop of my life!
There's no stopping the story!
They can keep their damn money.
You hear me?
This is a big mistake.
You're going to do as
you're told, is that clear?
It's Cypherball!
Why are you here?
To make sure that you obey
orders from the world government.
Freeze!
Don't mess with big news, Morgans!
If you know what's good for you!
When did this rouse get in here?
You know he's a government
official, right? Well aware.
It's time to boogie.
Now, we're compromised!
I may be a money-hungry Scrooge, but
above all, I'm a journalist first!
I get people's hearts dancing
with the stories I compose!
I'm a DJ of the press!
I decide what news is fit to print!
Mr. Morgans?
King Waffle of Drum Kingdom is calling.
He is.
What does he want?
It sounds like he has
some leaked information.
What?
What the heck?
A special report?
Don't cry.
It'll be okay.
Including the incident that the
government failed to keep under wraps.
The news report also
spread word of the decision
the leaders reached while at the reverend.
The disturbing news leaves
many in shock across the world.
Impossible!
This news can't be true!
Don't buy into this poppycock.
The W .E .J.'s either making
this up or taking bribes.
That bird is lying through
his smug little beak.
I just know it.
We're talking about Sabo.
He's got to be okay.
He's not dead. No way!
Take a deep breath.
Stay calm.
We need to confirm the facts.
We've lost contact with
our entire team, though.
Can we verify any of this?
Mom, please, Sabo.
You can't die.
Whoa, was she okay?
What was he doing in Marie Joie?
That's my brother for sure!
What's with Makino?
I don't know.
She closed the bar today.
Why there's so much chaos in the world?
Right now, I could really use a drink.
We only just found out that
he was still alive too.
How could this happen to you?
The world sure can't be a funny place.
There's never a boring day.
And we're just getting
to the good part now.
Week, Week.
Time to pack your bags.
If the Navy wants to get involved,
I'll just take it myself.
Jumping ahead to the present.
Koby, it's me.
Hold on, just a sec.
I need to find a better spot.
Sure.
Ah, that's right. The sea. The fog.
You're as diligent as ever, I see.
Well, I'm only following the
protocol is all, you know?
Oh, yeah.
By the way, I have an urgent
report for you, Captain.
You're serious?
That's the current state
of affairs out there?
Sadly, we're having trouble
keeping up with it all,
even with every active Marine on our side.
For your situation,
it's going as planned, so the
military won't be getting involved.
Not like we have the manpower anyway.
Probably for the best.
Wano and the world government
aren't allied regardless.
So, tell me what you knew about Big
Mom arriving at Onigashima. Gladly.
The Navy's banking on Kaido and Big Mom's
long-standing grudge to get explosive.
We're hoping those two
take each other out.
I thought so.
Hate to report this next bit, then.
I highly doubt we can count on them
being at each other's throats anymore.
It turns out they're teaming up.
Huh? What?
Are you joking with me? Huh?
As for Straw Hat Luffy, it's a stalemate.
There's been no news of his breakout.
I should also mention,
while I was in the capital the other
day, I happened to spot Cipher Pole Zero.
Why are they in Wano?
Really hoping I'm wrong about this,
but it would imply that the
government's colluding with
a pirate-ruled country to
conduct some nasty business.
I'm sure you're in a state of shock.
I was too when I found out.
in any case where are you now traveling
i'm on my way to the island of women
we're going to capture boa
hancock what the hell why
is there an entire fleet
crossing the calm belt wait
is that the Navy whatever
they want with us it can't
be good the news continued
to spread across the world
about time they should have
done this a long time ago
I know it was wrong to work
with pirates anyway let
them all die there were many
who celebrated the report
those dumb government lapdogs
are finally going away.
Screw you, Empress!
Screw you, Hawkeye!
Screw you,
Clown!
You good-for-nothing
looters can just piss off!
Those who had suffered at the hands of
pirates especially welcomed the news.
Really?
I'm no fan, but imagine how the war in
Marineford would have gone without them.
The nobles voted on this?
I bet the Navy acts right away.
Are you
absolutely certain about this?
But that was one of the three
great powers of the world.
However,
For those aware of their
involvement in the war of the best,
and those concerned about how the
distribution of power will fall,
the discovery was a
truly alarming situation.
The controversial article that
covered the events of this year's
reverie evoked many different
emotions from all ears who heard it.
But for better or for worse,
the abolition of the seven
warlords of the sea was absolute.
Before their dissolution,
the warlords consisted of many
of the world's strongest pirates.
Officially recognized
by the world government,
their crimes were
overlooked in exchange for
their use as deterrence
against other criminals.
As one might expect when dealing
with such volatile personalities,
the roster rotated over the years.
Former members include...
Crocodile.
After growing in power, he attempted
a coup in the kingdom of Alabasta.
Luckily,
Luffy was able to stop
him before he succeeded,
and he was expelled
from the Seven Warlords.
It didn't take long to replace him.
The man promoted to fill the
role was Marshal D. Teach.
However, that didn't last long.
He announced his resignation
after stealing Whitebeer's power.
Then there was the first
son of the sea, Jinbe,
whose sense of justice put
him at odds with the Navy.
He declared his departure
during the War of the Best.
Another former member was Gecko Moria.
This ghoulish figure, who had
a run-in with the Straw Hats,
also took part in the War of the Best.
However, after the skirmish, he
was deemed ill-suited for the role,
and the government sent
out men to eliminate him.
Then there's the heavenly
demon, Don Quixote do Flamingo.
He earned his notoriety for many reasons,
including overthrowing Dressrosa,
trafficking artificial devil fruits,
as well as being an
influential underground broker.
However,
his position in the system was revoked after
being defeated by Luffy and his allies.
One of which was Trafalgar Law,
another warlord of the sea. However,
thanks to his involvement in
the liberation of Dressrosa,
he too was stripped of his role.
There is another group of pirates
even more fearsome than the warlords.
The Four Emperors.
They are opposed by the
Marines of the Navy.
The Seven Warlords exist in the middle.
These three great powers have seemingly
kept peace in the world for many years.
However, two leaders emerged whose nations
had suffered because of the warlords.
King Nefertari Cobra of Alabasta,
and Rick Doldo III of Dressrosa.
They led a heartfelt
argument at the reverie.
The abolition of the Seven
Warlords system was their solution.
The matter was put to a
majority vote and passed.
As of this day, you no longer have
any ties to the world government.
All of your privileges
and rights as one of the
Seven Warlords have been
immediately revoked.
Is that clear?
Buggy, I know you're there.
You're nothing but a pirate again.
Oh, is any of this crap fair, huh?
First you declare me a warlord, then
you trick me around and take it away?
And now you want to arrest
me because you morons were
dumb enough to be scammed
by Crocodile and Doflamingo?
That has nothing to do with me!
Do you imbeciles even hear yourselves?
They have the whole coast surrounded.
We got a plan, boss?
These buzzkills are
screwing up my life plans!
What's going on here?
I thought the Navy was supposed
to be on our side, though.
What do you think we should do?
Hey, Mommy!
Surrender yourself at
once, Hawkeye and Mihawk!
Let's get this over with!
Snake Princess, we have a situation.
There's been a report your title as a
warlord of the sea has been ripped away.
Granny Magellan!
Navy ships are approaching
fast! Huh? Already?
This surely means trouble.
No, but that doesn't seem right.
Snake princess.
We have the advantage.
They've forgotten.
We're in it deep, Chairman Buggy.
Should we try to run?
Of course not!
We are going to give them
the fight of their lives!
It's time to get flashy!
You cowards!
That's what's happening for ya!
Boggy! Boggy! Boggy! Boggy!
Of cleansing us will be the
last mistake you ever make!
You can't say I didn't warn you!
Weevil!
Approval to give them hell!
Oh yeah, Mommy?
I'm gonna rip them apart then!
In the name of Whitebeard,
I'll stop all of you!
I feel a shudder of excitement.
It's been a long time.
I suppose I'm the one being chased now.
There's a good reason why we
were chosen to become warlords.
Because we're powerful.
Overwhelmingly so.
I'll be counting on you guys, all right?
Show them what we're made of.
While I get the hell out of here!